这是普通高等学校招生全国统一考试英语科听力部分。该部分分为第一、第二两节。注意，回答听力部分时，请。先将答案标在试卷上。听力部分结束前，你将有两分钟的时间将你的答案转涂到答题卡上。
Yes, certainly. Well, we're sort of a social club for people from different
countries. It's quite a new club.
We have about 50 members at the moment, but we're growing all the time.
That sounds interesting.
I'm British, actually, and I came to Washington about three months ago.
I'm looking for ways to meet people.
Mmm. What kinds of events do you organize?
Well, we have social get -togethers and sports events, and we also have language
evenings. Could you tell me something about the language evenings?
Yes. Every day except Thursday, we have a language evening.
People can come and practice their languages.
You know, over a drink or something.
We have different languages on different evenings.
Monday, Spanish, Tuesday,
Italian, Wednesday,
German, and Friday, French.
On Thursday, we usually have a meal in a restaurant, for anyone who wants to come.
Well, that sounds great.
I really need to my French.
OK. Well, if you can just give me your name and address, I'll send you the form and
some more information.
If you join now, you can have the first month free.
试音到此结束。听力考试正式开。开始，请看听力部分第一节。第一节，听下面五段对话。每段对话后有一个小题。从题中所给的
three A, B, and Read
三个选项中选出最佳选项。听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间来回答有。关小题和阅读下一小题，每段对话仅读一遍。例如，现在你有五秒钟的时间看试卷上的例题。你将听到以下内容：
Excuse me, can you tell me how much the shirt is?
Yes, it's 9.15.
你将有五秒钟的时间，将正确答案标在试卷上。衬衫的价格为九磅十五便士，所以你选择项，并将其标在试卷上。现在你有五秒钟的时间阅读第一小题的有关内容。
What are all these boxes for?
I'm looking for a new apartment.
Why? Well, just for a change.
And the rent is too high.
Wow! Jennifer got her new book published last month.
I learned it from the morning paper today.
Yes, I know.
It's based on her teaching experience in Africa last year.
Jim, have you seen Bob?
Not since he left my office an hour ago.
Why? He's supposed to be at the airport now to pick up Mr.
Anderson, but he's nowhere to be found.
Slow down a John.
Keep it under 65.
We don't want to be pulled over by the police.
Okay. I just wanted to get to the service station sooner.
I'm kind of hungry.
I found the gas bill in the mailbox.
How much is it?
About 150. Hello, Steve.
哦，它要过。昨天周五。不要担心，我明天就处理。第一节到此结束。第二节。别听下面五段对话或独白。每段对话或独白后有几个小题，从题中所给的三个选项中选出最佳选项。听每段对话。话或独白前，你将有时间阅读各个小题，每小题五秒钟。听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。每段对话或独白读两遍。听下面一段对话，回答第六和第七两个小题。现在你有十秒钟的时间阅读这两个小题。
How is your training going?
Great. My coach has a really good swim program for me, and I think I'm in first
-class condition. Do you have to get up very early?
Well, I don't like training early in the morning, so I start at ten.
I see. What about lunch, then?
I don't have lunch.
makes me sleepy.
I train all through the day until three.
Hello, Steve. How is your training going?
Great. My coach has a really good swim program for me, and I think I'm in first
-class condition. Do you have to get up very early?
Well, I don't like training early in the morning, so I start at ten.
I see. What about lunch, then?
I don't have lunch.
makes me sleepy.
I train all through the day until three.
Okay. Good evening, everyone.
听下面一段对话，回答第八至第十三个小题。现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
I'm Fiona. With us tonight is Mark, a famous local artist.
Thanks for joining us, Mark.
Thank you, Fiona.
Have you done live drawing before?
Is there more pressure to draw in front of an audience?
Yes. I have done live drawing before.
It's always fun.
I often draw pictures in pubs, and people always come over for a look and a chat.
I know that you've drawn pictures on many things, including maps and the covers of
books and magazines.
What's something you haven't drawn on yet, but really want to?
I'd like to draw on personal diaries people have kept over the years, and draw the
owner on it.
Fantastic. Could you also tell us where your inspirations come from?
Most are from the people I've met and talked to when I was traveling.
I always dreamed of traveling around the world and creating a series of drawings
about different cities in the world.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Fiona. With us tonight is Mark, a famous local artist.
Thanks for joining us, Mark.
Thank you, Fiona.
Have you done live drawing before?
Is there more pressure to draw in front of an audience?
Yes. I have done live drawing before.
It's always fun.
I often draw pictures in pubs, and people always come over for a look and a chat.
I know that you've drawn pictures on many things, including maps and the covers of
books and magazines.
What's something you haven't drawn on yet, but really want to?
I'd like to draw on personal diaries people have kept over the years, and draw the
owner on it.
Fantastic. Could you also tell us where your inspirations come from?
Most are from the people I've met and talked to when I was traveling.
I always dreamed of traveling around the and creating a series of drawings about
different cities in the world.
听下面一段对话，回答第十一至第十三三个小题。现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Hello? This is Carl's Cleaning.
May I help you?
Yes. I'm calling to ask about the cleaner position.
Is it still available?
Yes, it is.
We mainly work with small stores in the area, and the job is to clean the storefront
windows. I know.
You said that in the ad.
Do I need work experience?
No. We offer on -the -job paid training.
As a company car is provided, you must have a driver's license and a good driving
record. You also need to have a smartphone for communication.
Sure thing. Can I ask about the pay?
Certainly. It's ten to twelve dollars per hour, plus tips.
Okay. Do you have other requirements?
Our employees must be dependable, and be able to lift heavy things and stand long
hours at a time.
No problem. Good.
Can you come tomorrow afternoon at two for an interview?
Okay. This is Carl's Cleaning.
May I help you?
Yes. I'm calling to ask about the cleaner position.
Is it still available?
Yes, it is.
We mainly work with small stores in the area, and the job is to clean the storefront
windows. I know.
You said that in the ad.
Do I need work experience?
No. We offer on -the -job paid training.
As a company car is provided, you must have a driver's license and a good driving
record. You also need to have a smartphone for communication.
Sure thing. Can I ask about the pay?
Certainly. It's ten to twelve dollars per hour, plus tips.
Okay. Do you have other requirements?
Our employees must be dependable, and be able to heavy things and stand long hours
at a time.
No problem. Good.
Can you come tomorrow afternoon at two for an interview?
Okay. Good morning.
听下面一段对话，回答第十四至第十七四个小题。现在你有二十秒钟的时间阅读这四个小题。
Can I help you?
Yes. I've got a reservation.
My name is Hillary Langley.
Just a moment, please.
How do you spell your last name?
L -A -N -G -L -E -Y.
Langley. Well, I'm sorry, but we don't seem to have a reservation for you.
There must be some mistake.
I'm attending a conference in the city, and my secretary told me that the conference
organizer made the reservation for me.
I see. No, I'm sorry.
You are not booked in here.
Well, but can you find me a single room anyway?
I'm afraid there's nothing available at the moment.
Look, I really need a room here.
Can I talk to your manager?
The manager is away on business.
But, well, I may be able to help you if you could wait and prepare to check in after
two in the afternoon.
We'll have some rooms at that time.
That'd be very kind of you.
Could you give me a call when you have a room available?
I'll just wander around and have some coffee.
Certainly. Would you please give me your phone number?
Sure. Here's my card.
Thanks. Good morning.
Can I help you?
Yes. I've got a reservation.
My name is Hilary Langley.
Just a moment, please.
How do you spell your last name?
L -A -N -G -L -E -Y.
Langley. Well, I'm sorry, but we don't seem to have a reservation for you.
There must be some mistake.
I'm attending a conference in the city, and my secretary told me that the conference
organizer made the reservation for me.
I see. No, I'm sorry.
You are not booked in here.
Well, but can you find me a single room anyway?
I'm afraid there's nothing available at the moment.
I really need a room here.
Can I talk to your manager?
The manager is away on business.
But, well... I may be able to help you if you could wait and prepare to check in
after two in the afternoon.
We'll have some rooms at that time.
That'd be very kind of you.
Could you give me a call when you have a room available?
I'll just wander around and have some coffee.
Certainly. Would you please give me your phone number?
Sure. Here's my card.
Thanks. Good evening.
听下面一段独白，回答第十八至第二十三个小题。现在你有十五秒。中的时间阅读这三个小题
I'm honored to have my voice heard to make a difference in the lives of those little
birds that share our city.
My name is Christina.
I'm an enthusiastic birdwatcher.
Because we cut down too many trees in the nearby areas, many birds now find places
within the city to live.
The most common is the area behind the large advertisement boards on the poles.
It's a natural choice for the birds because the poles are similar to trees, tall and
far from dangers on the ground.
The surprising thing is that there are likely more than five or six kinds of birds
living together at each place.
While trying to learn more about these birds, I find that there have not been any
consistent studies or monitoring of them.
Their eating habits, adaptation to life in the city,
diseases, death rate and such other information are not available.
I'd like to suggest that a program be started to study these birds.
It could be convenient to employ birdwatchers to do the initial studies.
Good evening. I'm honored to have my voice heard to make a difference in the lives
of those little birds that share our city.
My name is Christina.
I'm an enthusiastic birdwatcher.
Because we cut down too many trees in the nearby areas, many birds now find places
within the city to live.
The most common is the area behind the large advertisement boards on the poles.
It's a natural choice for the birds because the poles are similar to trees, tall and
far from dangers on the ground.
It's natural program be started to study these birds.
It could be convenient to employ birdwatchers to do the initial studies.
第二节到此结束。现在你有两分钟的时间，将试卷上的答案转涂到答题卡上。
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
听力部分到此结束。